https://tulane.edu/privacy

Skip to main content
Tulane Home
Tulane Home
AboutHistory and TraditionsLeadership and AdministrationVisiting TulaneWhy TulaneFacts and FiguresAcademicsSchools and CollegeMajors and MinorsUndergraduate EducationGraduate EducationCommunity EngagementLibrariesSummer ProgramsPre-College ProgramsAcademic ResourcesAdmission & AidUndergraduate AdmissionGraduate AdmissionInternational AdmissionPart-Time StudiesCost and Financial AidVisit and ConnectResearchCOVID-19 ResearchCurrent ResearchHealth and BioinnovationGlobal StudiesEnvironment, Energy and ResilienceResearch in Real TimeCenters and InstitutesVice President for ResearchLife at TulaneCampus LifeEquity, Diversity and InclusionCity SmartsEntrepreneurship in NOLACelebrated EventsDestinations in NOLAArt and CultureCommitted to CommunityNews & EventsCOVID-19 In the NewsTulane TodayTulanian MagazineCalendar of EventsExpertsPress ReleasesOn Good Authority PodcastAthletics
AboutAboutHistory and TraditionsLeadership and AdministrationVisiting TulaneWhy TulaneFacts and FiguresAcademicsAcademicsSchools and CollegeMajors and MinorsUndergraduate EducationGraduate EducationCommunity EngagementLibrariesSummer ProgramsPre-College ProgramsAcademic ResourcesAdmission & AidAdmission & AidUndergraduate AdmissionGraduate AdmissionInternational AdmissionPart-Time StudiesCost and Financial AidVisit and ConnectResearchResearchCOVID-19 ResearchCurrent ResearchHealth and BioinnovationGlobal StudiesEnvironment, Energy and ResilienceResearch in Real TimeCenters and InstitutesVice President for ResearchLife at TulaneLife at TulaneCampus LifeEquity, Diversity and InclusionCity SmartsEntrepreneurship in NOLACelebrated EventsDestinations in NOLAArt and CultureCommitted to CommunityNews & EventsNews & EventsCOVID-19 In the NewsTulane TodayTulanian MagazineCalendar of EventsExpertsPress ReleasesOn Good Authority PodcastAthletics
Request Info
Visit
Apply
Give to Tulane
Alumni
Information For...
Close
Search form
Search
Search
Tulane A-Z
Close
>
Current Students
Privacy Notice
Tulane University is committed to respecting your privacy. You can visit official Tulane sites without revealing personal information. Should you choose to provide us with any personal information, you can be assured that it will be used only by Tulane University to conduct official university business, and personal information will not be disseminated to an unaffiliated third party.
Tulane uses IP addresses (the Internet address of your computer) to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our site. For instance, we run statistical software to identify those parts of our site that are most heavily used and which portion of our audience comes from within the Tulane network. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a visitor’s session will be logged, but the visitor will remain anonymous to us.
Like many other websites, portions of Tulane's site might use cookies. This is typically done to recognize you and your authorized access on the Tulane site. For instance, using cookies prevents an authorized user from needing to constantly reenter a password on every site of Tulane. These cookies get stored on your computer and do not contain personal data.
While aggregate statistical reports may be generated based on site usage, no personally identifiable information will ever be disseminated to any unaffiliated third party.
E-mail addresses appearing on Tulane sites are published for the sole purpose of facilitating private, individual communication between the university community and our visitors. Tulane specifically prohibits the automated harvesting of e-mail addresses from its site. Tulane will not distribute, sell or otherwise transfer addresses on its site or online services to any outside party whose intention is to initiate mass electronic mail messages. The university reserves the right to use internal search functions to obtain specific e-mail addresses for normal business operations or personal purposes.
Students wishing to suppress directory information in the Global Address List should visit the Registrar's Office, 110 Gibson Hall, to complete the necessary form. The "Request to prevent disclosure of directory information" form must be submitted in person along with a picture ID, which is copied and filed with the disclosure form in accordance with Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) guidelines.
By entering the Tulane University Campus, you understand that you may be photographed, filmed or videotaped, and you authorize Tulane the unqualified right to take pictures and/or recordings of you and grant the perpetual right to take your likeness, image, photo without compensation, for broadcast or use in any medium.
Tulane University GDPR Privacy Policy
